24小时
第三季  第20集
前情提要
各位已经有所了解
You have already been briefed on the Cordilla Virus
科迪利亚病毒正威胁我们的城市
that's now threatening our cities.
其中一管病毒已经被释放了
A vial of that virus has already been release.
我们查出了幕后主谋
We discovered the identity of the perpetrator.
他叫斯蒂芬 桑德斯 曾是英国军情6处的特工
His name is Stephen Saunders and he is a former MI6 agent.
在中东及亚洲的近30个国家里
In 32 countries across the Middle East and Asia,
你们的政府都雇有情报顾问
your government employs intelligence consultants.
他们是间谍
They're spies.
在45分钟内 我要他们的名单
In 45 minutes, I want a list of their identities.
如果你不从
If you fail to comply,
我会在主要城市散播两管病毒
I will release 2 vials of the virus in major cities.
桑德斯好像有个女儿
Looks like Saunders has a daughter.
他有个女儿?
A daughter?
她今年19岁 在圣巴巴拉上学
We know she is 19 years old, she goes to school in Santa Barbara.
我刚准备让圣巴巴拉警方把她带走
I was just about to call the Santa Barbara office to have her picked up.
托尼 这样不行
Tony, thats not the right play.
如果你想把她带来问话
If you want to grab her for questioning,
你必须瞒天过海
you are going to have to do it without him knowing,
也就是说 得偷梁换柱
which means we have to conduct a plain sight swap.
用我们的探员调包
Switch her out with one of our own agents.
好了 让我看看
Ok, let's see her.
金 你这样在近距离没法骗过熟悉简 桑德斯的人
Kim, you are not going to fool anyone who knows Jan Saunders up close.
我知道
I know.
好了
Clear.
你以为我在跟你开玩笑?
You think I am playing a game here with you?
成千上万的性命危在旦夕
Hundreds of thousands of people's lives are on the line.
为了让你合作 我什么都做得出
You have no idea how far I am willing to go to acquire your cooperation.
你父亲在哪 简?
Where is your father, Jane?
我不知道
I don't know.
你能帮我找些书吗?
Could you help me find something on this aisle?
可以 没问题
Yeah, no problem.
你敢呼救我就杀了你
Call for help and I will kill you right now.
金?
Kim?
该死的
Damn it.
桑德斯很快会知道我们抓了她女儿
Saunders is going to know we have his daughter.
以下事件发生于8点至9点之间
The following takes place between 8:00 am and 9:00 am.
这是我们一小时前设置的隔离区
These are the quarantine zones that were set up an hour ago.
再那之后 在银湖的一间急诊室又发现两起新增病例 汉考克公园也有一例
Since then, 2 new symptomatic patients were discovered at an ER in Silver Lake and one in Hancock Park.
这样又新增了5个隔离区
Those 2 cases engendered 5 new quarantine areas.
占全市面积的3%
Thats 3% of the city.
若隔离不彻底 隔离区还会成指数倍上增
If containment isn't total, it will grow exponentially.
好 谢谢 亚当
All right, thanks, Adam.
大家都很累了
We are all tired, I know that.
有人连续工作了24个小时
And some of you have been working for 24 hours straight.
情况有多紧急 也不必我多说
I don't have to tell you how serious the situation is,
我们不能有丝毫闪失
but we can't drift.
现在的情况糟得不能再糟了
If there ever was a worst case scenario, this is it.
我们已经深陷其中了
We are in it.
所有人必须坚守岗位
Everyone has to stay on point.
我们得从预防转向堵截
We have switched from prevention to containment.
病毒已经扩散
The virus is out.
你没事吧?
You all right?
我还好
Yeah, I am fine.
没想到会搞成这样 真对不起
I am sorry it had to go down like this.
我打中的那个人 死了吗?
The man I shot, is he dead?
嗯
Yeah.
接下来会怎样?
What's going to happen now?
桑德斯不久会知道我们抓了简
Saunders is going to know we have Jane.
我是杰克
This is Jack.
杰克 我是福雷斯特 那个叫桑德斯的女孩情绪已经稳定了
Jack, it's Forrester. The Saunders girl is calmed down.
你可以和她再谈谈
You can try talking to her again.
好的 谢谢 雷切尔
Ok, thanks, Rachel.
看看能不能从她那问出点什么
We will see what we can get from the daughter.
我明白 托尼 你来转告他?
I understand that, Tony. So you'll tell him?
好 我来告诉他
Yeah, I will tell him.
-采取所有防范措施  -稍后向您汇报
-I want every precaution taken.  -I'll get back to you.
好
Yeah.
杰克·鲍尔那边怎么样了?
What's going on with Jack Bauer?
这次行动没有完全成功
The operation wasn't completely successful.
大卫 他们确实抓到了桑德斯的女儿 但做的不是天衣无缝
Now, David, they do have Saunders' daughter, but they were unable to remain covert.
这么说 桑德斯知道了?
So, Saunders knows we have her?
还没有 但反恐局估计他不久就会发现
No, not yet, but CTU is estimating he will find out within the hour.
杰克有什么计划?
What's Jack's plan?
利用桑德斯的女儿 试着锁定他的位置
Use Saunders' daughter, try to locate him.
大卫 听着
David, listen.
离他给我们的期限还有15分钟
The deadline for his next demand is gonna be up here in about 15 minutes.
给他我们所有国外情报人员名单是叛国行为
Now, giving this guy a list of every foreign operative on our payroll is an act of treason.
我知道
I know that.
但如果不这么做他会继续放毒
But he will release more of the virus if we don't.
那你想怎么办?
So what do you want to do?
先看鲍尔从桑德斯女儿那问出了什么
I want to see what Bauer gets out of Saunders' daughter first.
你知道刚才发生了什么吗?
You know what just happened?
你父亲雇来保护你的人想杀死我们的探员
A man who your father hired to protect you just tried to kill one of my agents.
这么说 你们杀了他?
So, you killed him, right?
那个我父亲的手下
A man that worked for my father.
你很聪明 简
You are a smart girl, Jane.
看看那边
Look out in that room.
这里全是极力保护美国公民的联邦探员
Everyone here is a federal agent whose job is to protect the lives of American citizens.
简 我知道你很难相信
Jane, I know how hard it must be for you to believe
你所听到的你父亲的事
everything that everybody's been telling you about your father.
但我给你看点东西 你就会改变主意
But I am going to show you something that will change your mind.
越早配合 你越早能帮我们拯救生灵
And the sooner you stop resisting me, the sooner you can help us start saving lives.
为什么把希望放在我身上?
Why are you putting all this on me?
因为你是斯蒂芬 桑德斯的女儿
Because you are Stephen Saunders' daughter.
不幸的是 你是我们唯一能和他对抗的筹码
And unfortunately, you are the only leverage we have against him.
你别以为你说了这些离谱的话 我就会相信你
You cant just say these outrageous things and expect me to believe you.
我知道
I know.
事实上 我认识你父亲
Truth is, I know your father.
我曾和他共事过
I worked with him.
他曾是个很好的人
He was a good man.
很勇敢的人
He was a brave man.
但他遭遇了些变故
But something has happened to him.
我现在只想阻止他的所作所为
All I care about right now is stopping him from doing what he is doing.
没你的帮助我办不到
I can't do that without you. I need your help.
帕默尔还没把名单交出来
Palmer still hasn't sent the list yet.
他还有15分钟
He has 15 more minutes.
反恐局正通过域名锁定IP地址 想由此找到你
CTU has been trying to use IP locators to get at you through the domain name.
我们有防备 对吧?
We've protected it though, right?
对 那是条死胡同
Yes. It's a dead end.
好
Good.
谢谢
Thank you.
我让你看看你父亲是个什么样的人
I am going to show you who your father really is.
这是我们8年前拍的照片
These photographs were taken over 8 years ago.
你父亲告诉你母亲他到欧洲执行一项找寻任务
Your father told your mother that he was going to Europe on a fact finding mission.
但实际上 我们都是特别行动队的
But the truth of the matter is, we were both part of a special forces unit
那次我们被派往科索沃 去刺杀一个叫维克托里 德拉赞的人
that was dispatched to Kosovo to kill a man named Victor Drazen.
这是任务结束的地方 德拉赞的藏身处
This is where the mission ended, Drazens' hideout.
当我离开科索沃的时候 以为你父亲在爆炸中身亡了
When I left Kosovo, I believed your father had died in the blast.
英国政府也是这样告诉你母亲的
The British government told your mother that thats where he died, too.
但最近 我们通过电话记录发现
But recently, we discovered through phone records
你父亲4年前曾和你联系过
that your father had contacted you 4 years ago
告诉你他还活着 对吧?
to tell you he was still alive. Is that right?
对
Yes.
我母亲去世几个月后 我接到他的电话
A couple of months after my mother died, I get a call from him.
他说在欧洲隐姓埋名活了下来
He said he was living in Europe under an assumed name.
没人知道他还活着
And that nobody knew he was alive.
为了他的安全 我不能告诉任何人曾和他联系过
And for his protection, I couldn't tell anyone that I had spoken to him.
他有没有告诉你为何多年后突然跟你联系?
Did he ever tell you why he had contacted you after so many years?
有
Yes.
他说他想我
He missed me.
我能理解
I understand that.
几个小时前我们从国际警察那里得到了些资料
Over the last 3 to 4 hours, we have been pooling data from Interpol.
有些近期的照片
Here are some more recent images.
这张是你父亲和赛义德·阿里在一起的照片 他是中东有名的军火商
This is your father with Sayed Ali, a known weapon dealer in the Middle East.
这张是他和雅加达的生物学家Ari Consul会见的照片
Here you see his meeting with Ari Consul, a biologist from Jakarta
后者因制造非法生化武器被判处终身监禁
who is now spending the rest of his life in prison for the manufacturing of illegal biological weapons.
这说明不了什么 他与他们见面可以有很多种原因
This doesn't prove anything. He could have been meeting with these people for any number of reasons.
我给你放一段录音 是我们今天早上获取的三个中的一个
I will play you an audio file, one of three that we got from your father earlier today.
这是你父亲和美国总统的谈话
This is your father talking to the President of the United States.
...按照美国这个战争机器的吩咐和自己的国家作对
...Working against these countries at the behest of the American military machine.
在45分钟内 我要你把他们的身份通过Sylviaimports.com传给我
In 45 minutes, I want a list of their identities sent to me by way of a website, sylviaimports.com.
如果你不从 我会在主要城市散播两管病毒
If you fail to comply, I will release 2 vials of the virus in major cities.
再释放两管 他已经释放了一管
2 more vials of the virus. He has already released one.
这是洛杉矶的钱德勒 广场酒店的现场影像资料
This is a live video feed from the Chandler Plaza Hotel in Los Angeles,
就是你父亲选择
where your father ordered the release of one if the vials of the virus
在通风系统释放病毒的酒店
into the ventilation system of the hotel.
这些你看到的人会在2到3个小时内死亡
The people that you are looking at will all be dead within the next 2 to 3 hours.
那里大约有800人 简
There is almost 800 of them, Jane.
他们将这么死去
This is how they will die.
我不想看下去了
I don't want to see any more.
我也不想看下去了
I don't want to see any more, either.
你能帮助我们阻止他 简 拜托
You can help us stop this, Jane, please.
拜托
Please.
我有个电话号码
I have a phone number.
他告诉我不管何时如果有麻烦 就拨这个号码
He told me to call it day or night if I ever got in trouble.
你以前用过吗?
Have you ever used it before?
没有
No.
告诉我们
We need it.
不
No.
肯定搞错了
It's a mistake.
我很好
I am ok.
我没被感染
I don't have any infection.
不 别把我和他们放在一起
No. Don't take me in there with those people.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
求求你们
Please.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
米歇尔 我刚接到电话
Michelle, I just got a call.
你的检测结果正送过来
Your lab results are on the way here.
很抱歉打断您 总统先生
I am sorry to interrupt, Mr President.
怎么回事? 亚伦?
What's this? Aaron?
局长刚才通知我卫生局认为洛杉矶处于危险之中
Our bureau chief just informed me that NHS believes Los Angeles is no longer safe.
我们得将您转移
We would like to move you out of the state.
谢谢你们的关心
I appreciate your concern.
告诉库兹曼局长 我想在这处理事情
Tell Chief Kurtzman, I'd rather manage matters from here.
先生 恐怕不能如你所愿
Sir, I am afraid this isn't a request.
什么
Excuse me.
特勤处正在调用各区的人手
Secret service is invoking section 32.
对你进行保护 请您和我们一起到空军一号上去
For your own protection, we are requiring you to accompany us to Air Force One.
你在命令我吗?
You are ordering me?
是的 为了您的安全
Yes sir. It's for your safety.
韦恩?
Wayne?
我不知道命令的细节 但特勤处确实已经在抽调人手
I don't know the specifics of the code, but Secret Service is invoking it.
而且在洛杉矶 真的非常危险
And here in LA, the threat is serious.
哪里都很危险
It's serious everywhere.
至少在这 我们知道所面对的是什么
At least here, we know what we are facing.
谁有权解除命令 亚伦?
Who has to sign off on this, Aaron?
库兹曼局长和我
Chief Kurtzman and myself.
我们俩单独谈谈 亚伦
I'd like a word in private with you, Aaron.
先生 很抱歉我有些失礼
Sir, I am sorry for appearing to overstep my bounds.
但保护您是我的职责
But it's my job to protect you.
听着 亚伦
Listen, Aaron.
你跟了我多年
You have been with me from the beginning.
你尽职尽责 不需要道歉
You don't have to apologize for doing your job.
但危机会过去的
But this crisis will end.
如果知道总统和他们同生死共患难 这个城市的人民以及这个国家会更坚强
And the people in this city and this country will be stronger, knowing that their president stood by them shoulder to shoulder.
我以一个朋友的身份请求你
I am asking you as a friend and a fellow citizen.
保护我 但就在洛杉矶
Protect me, but here in Los Angeles.
你愿意吗?
Can you do that for me?
好吧 先生 为您我愿这么做
Yes, sir. For you I can.
谢谢
Thank you.
遵命
Yes, sir.
总统先生 电话会议已准备好
Mr. President the conference call is about to begin.
杰克 你在吗?
Jack, you there?
是的 我在
Yeah, I am on.
总统先生?
Mr President?
阿尔梅达先生 我已经得知
Mr Almeida, I understand.
也许有一条途径可以找到斯蒂芬 桑德斯
We may have a way to locate this man, Stephen Saunders.
是的 但我的技术人员告诉我可能要花费15分钟甚至更久的时间
We do, sir. However, my technical staff just informed me that to do this properly, it may take 15 minutes, possibly longer.
这么说在剩下的时间里没办法找到他?
So there is no way we can get to him in the next few minutes?
是的 没错
No, sir. There's not.
好吧 诸位 我们没时间了
Ok, gentlemen, time is upon us.
深思熟虑后 我觉得我们只能放手一搏
Having considered all the possible scenarios, I see no other choice than to draw our line in the sand.
我不会再向桑德斯妥协了
I will not give in to Saunders' latest demand.
总统先生 我希望您明白 如此一来 我们只有一条路可选了
Mr President, I hope you understand that leaves us with only one option.
拿斯蒂芬 桑德斯的女儿做人质 希望这样能制止他
That's to use Stephen Saunders' daughter as a hostage and hope that will stop him.
我明白
I understand.
好吧 各位 就这么办吧
All right, gentlemen, get to it.
遵命
Yes, sir.
大卫 你肯定我们这么做是对的?
David, are you sure we are doing the right thing?
我唯一肯定的是我们不能让这个国家任这个疯子摆布
The only thing I am sure of is we can't let this country be taken over by this madman.
杰克 你想怎么做?
Jack, how do you want to do this?
要拖住他多久才能追踪到?
How long do we have to keep him on the line so we can run a trace?
大约一分钟
About a minute.
好 我们得先隐藏这个指挥部
Ok, we need to cover our bases.
我们利用简在电话上拖住他 如果需要行动 随时准备
We will use Jane to try and keep him on the line. If we have to jump in, we will.
好 我会负责追踪 你告诉简该怎么做
All right, look, I will initiate the trace. You tell Jane what we need her to do.
再联络
I will get back to you.
该死的
Damn it.
怎么了?
What's happening?
我们没时间了 你得给你父亲打个电话
We have run out of time. We need you to call your father.
和他说什么?
And tell him what?
随便 只要尽量拖延时间
Anything. We just want you to keep him on the line.
多久?
For how long?
至少一分钟
At least a minute.
你能做到吗?
Do you think you do that?
我想考虑一下
I need to think about it.
简 我们的时间不多了
Jane, we don't have anymore time.
你父亲威胁几分钟后会继续释放病毒
Your father just threatened to release more of the virus in the next few minutes.
名单发来了吗?
Is the list up, yet?
没有
No.
好吧 时间到了
Well, his time is up.
喂?
Yeah?
是我
It's me.
释放旧金山的病毒
Release San Francisco.
是我女儿
That's my daughter's line.
伊恩 等等
Ian, wait.
我等会给你电话
I will call you right back.
找出这个电话的位置
Find out where this is coming from.
简?
Jane?
对
Yeah.
嗨 爸爸
Hi, Dad.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我告诉过你 若非紧急不要拨这个号码
I told you only to use this number in an emergency.
我想见你 我很害怕
I want to see you. I am scared.
所有机场都关闭了 新闻上一直都在谈论警报等级上升的事
All the airports are shut down, and the news channels are talking about the alert level being raised.
待在你那别乱跑 宝贝
Just, just stay where you are, honey.
你不会有事的
You'll be fine.
有人在追踪这个电话
Someone is monitoring the call.
我先挂了 宝贝
Hang on a second, honey.
你肯定?
Are you sure?
对
Yes.
信号一闪而过
The signal is splitting.
他们抓了她
They've got her.
杰克 我们的追踪线路被发现了
Jack, we just got a hit on the trace route.
他发现我们在监听
He knows we are on the phone.
如果他打回来我怎么办?
What do I do when he gets back on?
没关系 你做的很好 继续说话就行了
Nothing. You are doing great. Just keep talking.
简
Jane.
爸爸
Yes, Dad.
有个叫杰克·鲍尔的人在你旁边 是吗?
There's a man named Jack Bauer with you, isn't there?
你说什么 爸爸?
What, Dad?
把电话给他
Hand the phone to him.
爸爸
Dad.
照我说的做
You heard me.
你说吧 斯蒂芬
I am on the line, Stephen.
杰克 你清楚我有多少病毒 也知道我会做出什么
Jack, you know how many vials I have, and what I am capable of.
你也知道我会做出什么
And you know what I am capable of, too.
追踪到了吗?
Did you get a lock on the signal?
没有 我们的定位失败了
It's dead. We are negative for passive triangulation.
托尼 查到了吗?
Tony, did you get him?
还在查 亚当?
We are working on it, Adam?
我得到了两个微波信号可以提供经度信息 但还缺少纬度信息
I have got 2 microwaves that can give me a longitude reading, but I don't have the latitude yet.
这儿 试试这个
Here, try this.
亚当?
Adam?
我在试 托尼 我正在查
I am trying, Tony. I am working on it.
好了 有了 柯林斯街区21904号
Ok, here it is: 21904 Collins.
找到他了 杰克 马上派人过去
We have got him, Jack. We will send teams from here.
好 把具体位置发送到直升机上
Ok. Patch the location through to the chopper.
我们马上登机
We will be airborne in minutes.
给我接通蔡斯的电话
Get me Chase.
找到了 通知直升机过来
We got a location. Tell the chopper to come in.
马上集合队伍
I want you to assemble the team.
把简带回反恐局 一定要保护好她
Take Jane back to CTU. I want her fully protected.
你准备对我父亲做什么?
What are you going to do to my father?
我准备去阻止他
I am going to stop him.
我要你陪着她
I want you to go with her.
米歇尔
Michelle.
检测结果刚送到
The test results, they just came in.
谢谢
Thank you.
阿尔梅达
Almeida.
宝贝 是我
Honey, it's me.
你怎么样?
What's going on?
我没事了
I am ok.
我没被感染
I am not infected.
你肯定?
Are you sure?
他们做了AA测试和血液检测 我都正常
Yeah. They did AA swab and a blood test and I am going to be fine.
我没事了
I am going to be fine.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my god.
哦 我的上帝 亲爱的 太好了
Oh, my god, sweetheart, that's fantastic.
听着 马上从那离开
Look, I want you to get out of there right now.
好吗 远离那些感染了的人
Ok? Away from anybody who's infected.
哦 不 不 不 亲爱的
Oh, no, no, no, sweetheart.
他们说我们没有感染 说明对病毒有免疫性
They said those of us that didn't come down with the infection, that we have an immunity to the virus.
那他们带你去哪?
Well, where are they taking you?
市区 卫生署
Downtown, to NHS.
他们准备对我们进行18个小时的观察
They want to keep us under watch for 18 hours.
但他们说这只是例行程序
But they said it's just a formality.
好 我会尽快赶去 好吗?
All right, look. I will get there as soon as I can, all right?
不 不
No, no.
别过来 反恐局需要你
Stay where you are. They need you at CTU.
在市区里 我也能工作
I can work from downtown.
宝贝 你不必工作
Honey, you don't have to work.
我们能应付的来
We can handle it from here.
我想帮忙 托尼
I want to help, Tony.
好吧
Ok.
米歇尔.
Michelle
嗯
Yeah.
我不敢相信我差点就要失去你
I can't believe I almost lost you.
我也差点失去你
I almost lost you, too.
但我们还是好好的
But we are still here.
对
Yeah.
我得走了
I have to go.
-到了卫生署 我会给你电话的  -嘿...
-I will call you from NHS.  -Hey...
我爱你
I love you.
我也好爱你
I love you so much.
打扰一下 各位 请听我说几句 好吗?
Excuse me, everybody, can I have your attention, please?
总统先生要求各位不要使用摄像机和录音设备
The President has asked you to this informal setting without cameras or recording devices
他将解释钱德勒 广场酒店事件是否与关闭机场有关
to tell you what relationship, if any the outbreak at the Chandler Plaza Hotel has with the airport closures.
钱德勒 广场酒店是不是警报等级提高的原因?
Was the Chandler Plaza the reason yellow level was raised?
总统先生会在声明中解释清楚
The President will deal with that in his statement.
这么说桑德斯知道我们抓了她女儿?
So Saunders knows we have his daughter.
对
Yeah.
大概5分钟前发现的
Found out about 5 minutes ago.
他有什么反应?
How did he react?
他中止了通信
He broke off communication.
好消息是 反恐局找到了桑德斯的位置 他们已经派人过去了
The good news is, CTU has position of Saunders, and they are sending in teams now.
有多大把握?
What's our confidence level?
大卫 这个人对我们了如指掌
David, this man knows our system, our protocols.
他肯定会负隅顽抗
He is going to be tough to corner.
所有应急部队保持警惕
Stay on top of our emergency response teams.
拿他女儿做人质可能会把事情弄糟
The abduction of his daughter may have made things worse.
有请总统先生
The President of United States.
诸位请坐
Please be seated.
正如大家所知道的 今天早上警报等级已提高至红色
As you know, this morning our alert level was raised to red.
我们的确得到了美国可能面临生化攻击的情报
We do have information regarding a possible biological attack on American soil.
我们已尽最大努力做好全国防范
We have maximized our preparedness across the nation.
当前人们保护自身安全的最好办法就是待在家里
Now the best way for our citizens to insure their own safety is to stay home.
如果你还在上班 赶快回家
If you are at work, go home.
这是我希望诸位媒体报道的
That's the message I hope the media can convey.
总统先生 我们听说英国情报机构驻本地办事处几小时前被袭击了
Mr President, we have heard reports that the local British intelligence office was attacked a couple hours ago.
是否与此有关?
Is that related?
我暂时不能透露更多的细节
I can't release any details on that right now.
很抱歉 总统先生 洛杉矶的市民正在陷入恐慌
I am sorry. Mr President, the people of the city of Los Angeles are starting to panic.
官方始终守口如瓶
And information is not following from this office.
听说病毒爆发 到处是隔离区 现在又有了生化攻击的暗示
We have had major outbreaks, we have had quarantines, and now a hint of biological terror.
卡罗尔 别这样
Carol, Please,
不 格里 不 总统不能再含糊其辞了
No. Gerry, no. The President has got to be more forthcoming.
没事的
It's ok.
即便是总统也必须配合 你也一样
The President has to be in control, and so do you.
如果诸位希望尽职尽责 帮助公众 请安静的听我说完
If you want to help the public and do your jobs best, sit quietly and listen to what I have to say.
生化武器在人口密集的地方造成的伤害最大
Biological agents do their worst damage where large groups of people congregate.
当前我们最好的防范措施就是劝说所有人回到家中 等待新的指令
The best defense we have right now is to encourage everyone to go home and stay home and await further instructions.
蔡斯 我是杰克 你在路上了吗?
Chase, it's Jack. Are you en route?
对 十多分钟后到
Yeah, I am a little more than 10 minutes out.
杰克 桑德斯有没有可能知道我们已经掌握了他的位置?
Jack, what are the chances Saunders knows we have his location?
不太可能 桑德斯应该认为必须通话超过90秒才能锁定位置
Not likely. Saunders will think he had 90 seconds more of talk time before we could ever lock onto this location.
听着 尽快到达指定位置 提醒当地警方保持隐蔽
Look, I want you to move your teams into position and remind local law enforcement to stay out of sight.
不能让他逃了
We can't tip him off.
明白
Done.
亚当 我要你盯着卫星 注意每一个进出楼房的人 并把资料发给当地警方
Adam, I want you to keep an eye on the satellite, track anyone coming in and out of that building, and feed all that information over to local law enforcement.
听见了吗?
You copy?
我正在盯着呢 杰克
I am watching the data now, Jack.
好的 让克萝伊也来帮忙
Ok, plug Chloe into it, too.
好
Yeah.
听着 各位 机会来了 好好把握
Listen, everybody, this is our time. Get it right.
斯蒂芬 我们必须撤了
Stephen, we have to leave.
我们哪也不去
We are not leaving.
为什么?
Why not?
你说他们可能知道了我们的位置
You said they probably have our location now.
不是可能 他们已经知道了
Not probably. They do.
我不明白
I don't understand.
他们从卫星上发现了我们
They have got us on satellite.
如果我们现在离开肯定逃不出他们的手掌心
They will pick us up if we try to leave now.
那我们就待在这等着被包围?
So we sit around here and wait till they surround us?
对
Exactly.
他们来的人越多 我们越容易逃走
The more bodies they send, the easier it will be for us to disappear.
不 我不在这坐以待毙
No. I am not waiting around to get caught.
奥斯特兰.
Osterlind
我要走了 斯蒂芬
I am leaving, Stephen.
请说
Yeah.
她出发了吗?
Has she left, yet?
还没
No.
快了
She will.
盯着她
Stay on her.
必须尽快拿下
We are going to need to do this soon.
好的
Ok.
我们去哪?
Where are we going?
洛杉矶
Los Angeles.
你父亲说过那里有病毒
I thought your father said there was an outbreak there.
我们要去的地方很安全 不必担心
Where we are going, it'll be safe. Don't worry.
他们打算把我带到洛杉矶什么地方?
Where in Los Angeles are they taking me?
一个叫反恐局的地方
A place called CTU.
反恐局?
CTU?
对
Yeah.
反恐局
Counter Terrorist Unit.
我还是不敢相信
I still can't believe this.
我父亲竟是恐怖分子
That my father is a terrorist.
4年前 当我得知他还活着的时候 我是那么开心
4 years ago, when I found out he was alive after all that time, I was so happy.
我有父亲了
I had a father.
我相信他说的一切
I let myself believe all that he wanted me to.
相信他是个很好的人
That he was this wonderful man.
你们多长时间见一次面?
How often did you see him?
一年大概几次
Couple times a year.
有时会给我惊喜
Sometimes he'd surprise me.
他总给我带来礼物
And he'd always bring me something.
非常棒的礼物
And it was always perfect.
仿佛他知道我的心思一样
Like he knew.
也许他确实知道
Maybe he did know.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
他派人暗中监视你 简
He had people watching you, Jane.
他甚至比你自己还清楚你的一切
He knew more about your life than you are probably aware of.
我该怎么面对他?
What am I supposed to do with all these feeling for him?
我爱的那个父亲根本就不存在
The person I love doesn't even exist.
他会怎么样?
What's going to happen to him?
我爸爸正争取抓住他
My dad's going to try and bring him in.
亚当 我是杰克
Adam, it's Jack.
桑德斯那里的情况怎么样?
What's the status of Saunders' location?
我一直在盯着 杰克 没人离开这栋楼
I am watching it now, Jack. No one's left the building.
哪个部门协助我们?
Who's working with us?
洛杉矶警局在一个街区外设置了警戒区
LAPD has set up a staging area about a block away.
他们秘密包围了这里
They have surrounded the area and are hidden from view.
好的 干的好
Ok, good work.
告诉他们我马上就到
Tell them I will be there in a few minutes.
好的
All right.
对
Yeah.
你说得很对
You're absolutely sure.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
托尼 我要和你谈谈
Tony, I need to talk to you.
就一会儿
Yeah, just a second.
为什么不把这些模拟结果传到我电脑里
Why don't you go ahead and put these simulations on my system.
我现在就要和你谈谈
I need to talk to you right now.
我们待会再说 你们先继续
I will catch up. Go ahead.
什么事?
What's it?
你也知道 我一直在负责隔离区的事情
I have been working on the tented quarantine area, you know.
怎么了?
And?
我又检查了被隔离人员的名单 发现了一个熟悉的名字
I have been going over the list of people who have been isolated and I found a familiar name.
谁?
And?
是萨拉 考夫曼
One of them was Sarah Kaufman.
萨拉 考夫曼是谁?
Who is Sarah Kaufman?
亚当的姐姐
Adam's sister.
你确定是亚当的姐姐?
You are sure it's Adam's sister?
对 她检测结果是阳性
Yeah. She tested positive in the medical sense.
她快死了
She's going to die.
好吧 谢谢
All right, thanks.
你不会告诉他的 对吗?
You are not going to tell him, are you?
不 我必须告诉他
Yeah, I have to.
但我们还有很多工作要做
But we still have a lot of work to do.
如果得知他姐姐数小时后就会死去 他怎么还会有心思工作?
I mean, how can he concentrate knowing that his sister gonna die in a couple hours?
你想过没有?
Did you ever think about that?
克萝伊 我受够你了
Chloe, I am getting real tired of your personality.
我只是想帮忙
I am just trying to help.
你想帮忙? 那就回去工作
You want to help? Get back to work.
亚当 能来一下好吗?
Adam, could you come with me a second?
我正在帮杰克收集卫星资料 能等一下吗?
I am sitting on these satellite feeds for Jack right now. Can it wait?
不 不行
No, it can't.
克萝伊会看着的
Chloe will watch it.
好吧 什么事?
Fine. What is it?
托尼 我得一直盯着
Tony, I really have to stay on this.
有点私事 跟我来
It's personal. Just come with me.
托尼 不管什么事 你直说好了 我做错了什么事吗?
Tony, whatever it is, just tell me. Did I do anything wrong?
没有
No.
恐怕我要告诉你一些不幸的消息
I am afraid I have some bad news for you.
你的姐姐 萨拉 在其中的一个隔离区里
Your sister, Sarah, is in one of the quarantine zones.
什么?
What?
你有个姐姐叫萨拉 对吧?
You have a sister named Sarah, right?
对
Yeah.
但他们怎么确定是我姐姐? 洛杉矶有上百个萨拉 考夫曼
But how can they be sure that it's her? There have to a hundred Sarah Kaufman.in Los Angeles.
克萝伊核实了
Chloe confirmed it.
她有没有和那些感染的人隔开?
Have they kept her away from the people that are infected?
她也感染了
She's infected.
你说什么 托尼?
What are you saying, Tony?
你意思是萨拉也快死了?
Are you telling me that Sarah's going to die?
恐怕是这样
It looks that way, yeah.
我很抱歉
I am sorry.
哦 上帝
Oh, my god.
亚当我会给你个机会跟你姐姐说说话 但之后你必须专心工作直到这件事结束
Adam, I am going to give you a chance to talk to your sister, but then I am going to need you to stay on until the crisis passes.
你能做到吗?
You think you can do that?
亚当.
Adam
因为我们需要你
Because we need you here.
好吧
Yeah.
好的
All right.
不 我已完全被包围
No, I am completely surrounded.
你怎么知道的?
How do you know?
街对面的保安每15分钟就会巡逻一圈
There was a security guard across the street making his rounds every 15 minutes.
但很久没人来了 这说明反恐局已经控制了那栋楼
He missed his last rotation, which means CTU has taken over that building.
你打算怎么办?
What are you going to do?
我准备在这等着鲍尔来
I am going to wait until Bauer gets here.
贝克和他的人在大楼后面布防
Baker and his team are running operations from behind the building.
接到我们的指令 他们就会行动
They will move when we tell them to.
洛杉矶警局在这里设置了警戒区 还有这儿 这儿和这儿
LAPD set up a perimeter here, here, here and here.
特警队会从这里攻进去
We got SWAT teams moving in this way and from over here.
狙击手在屋顶
Snipers on the roof.
没有命令 不准轻举妄动 明白吗?
Nobody goes until we give the word. Understand?
情况怎么样?
What's the situation?
我们已经包围了这栋楼
We have taken over building on either side of him.
狙击手安排在屋顶 已经就绪
We got snipers on the roof, ready to go.
电话有没有屏蔽?
Phones?
没有屏蔽这里 你说过会惊动他
We didn't jam the area.You said he'd know.
用红外线探测过没有?
What about infrared?
红外线穿不过这些墙 杰克
We can't get through those walls, Jack.
他知道我们来了
He knows we are here.
你怎么知道?
What makes you say that?
换成我也感觉的出
Because I would.
你觉得他还在里面?
You think he's still in there?
对
Yeah.
他为什么不逃?
Why wouldn't he try to escape?
我不知道
I don't know.
好 一旦我发出信号 所有人员就要全部就位
All right, on my signal I want you move your teams into position.
每个出口至少3人
Minimum 3 men per exit.
记住 没有我的命令不准擅自冲进屋内
Remember, no one goes into the builder till I give the order.
我们必须考虑到桑德斯有所防范
We have to assume Saunders has taken defensive measures.
大家准备好了吗?
Everybody ready?
上
Let's go.
所有人立刻就位 开始行动
All team move into first position. This is a go.
重复一遍 开始行动
Repeat, this is a go.
-所有人员已就位  -好的 我们上
-Positions all set  - OK, Let's go.
斯蒂芬 桑德斯.
Stephen Saunders
我是杰克·鲍尔
This is Jack Bauer.
你已完全被包围
You are completely surrounded.
总统不会再屈服于你的要求了
The President is refusing to capitulate to any further demands.
我得提醒你 你女儿还在我们手上
I need to remind you that we still have your daughter.
斯蒂芬.
Stephen
结束了
It's over.
你现在唯一的活路就是放弃抵抗 双手抱头走出大门
The only way you are getting out of this thing alive is coming through the front door with your hands on your head.
没那么容易 杰克
That's not exactly true, Jack.
亚当.
Adam
现在不行 克萝伊 我正在负责抓捕桑德斯的通信联络
Not now, Chloe. I am running comm on the Saunders pickup.
我知道你在做什么
I know what you are doing.
Robin 你先帮亚当盯一会 你跟我来
Robin, take over Adam's screen for a minute. Come here.
为什么? 克萝伊 现在真不是时候
Why? Chloe, this is really not a good time.
托尼 我有事请要汇报
Tony, you need to hear this.
什么?
What?
有些不好的消息
I have to report some bad news.
因为亚当忘了屏蔽频道 外勤部队失去了两个卫星的数据
Field ops lost 2 satellite feeds because Adam forgot to segregate the channels.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
是真的 我检查了你的系统
It's true. I checked your system.
我得仔细检查一切
I had to reinitiate everything.
你动了我系统?
You touched my system?
托尼 你要面对现实
Tony, let's face it.
亚当不该在这
Adam shouldn't be here.
他姐姐生命垂危 他在这心神不宁
He's under duress because his sister's going to die.
我没忘记屏蔽频道 托尼
I did not forget to separate those channels, Tony.
不 你忘了
Yes, you did.
好了 听着 没时间管这些了
All right, look, we don't have time for this.
还有2组人马在等着我们
We have teams on the ground that are depending on us.
你有没有恢复卫星资料?
Did you back up the satellite data?
有 我重新设置了一切
Yes. I reprogrammed almost everything.
我们大约丢失了30秒
We lost about 30 seconds.
没有的事 克萝伊
We didn't lose it, Chloe.
我现在就能证明给你看
I can prove it to you right now.
我记得我...
I thought that I...
克萝伊是对的
Chloe is right.
我是忘了屏蔽频道了
I forgot to separate them.
好吧 听着
All right, look.
你犯了个错
You made a mistake.
但我得知道此后你能否保证不再犯类似的错
But what I need to know is if can you get through the rest of the day without making another one.
亚当?
Adam?
我没事 托尼
I'm fine, Tony.
好
Ok.
我想要你知道我不同意托尼的决定
I want you to know that I don't agree with Tony's decision.
你留下来继续 我就得每隔10分钟复查一遍你的工作 防止你再犯错
But since you are going to stay, I am going to double check your logs every 10 minutes in case you screw up again.
杰克 你打算怎么办?
Jack, what do you want to do?
如果他不在里面 我们就是在浪费时间
If he's not in there, we are wasting a lot of time we don't have.
原地待命
Just have the men maintain their position.
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
恭喜你 杰克
Congratulations, Jack.
你找到我了
You found me.
斯蒂芬 结束了 赶紧出来
Stephen, it's over. Come on out.
还是你进来抓我比较好
It would suit me better if you came in here and got me.
我不喜欢这么多的反恐局狙击手拿枪瞄着我
I'd hate to be in the crosshairs of all those unstable CTU snipers.
双手抱头走出大门
Come out the front door with your hands on your head.
我保证你不会有事
I assure you, you'll be fine.
11管病毒 上百万条命
11 more vials, millions dead.
你还是不为所动?
That doesn't affect your nerves a little bit?
总统先生说的很清楚
The President has made himself clear.
他不再任你摆布
He's not following orders from you anymore.
我为他工作
I work for him.
好吧 如果是这样 请让我仔细考虑一下
Well, if that's the case, you won't mind if I take a few minutes to think things over.
你考虑的时候 顺便把你的女儿也考虑进去
While you are thinking things over, you might want to take a second and think about your daughter.
托尼确定了他就在这栋楼里
Tony just confirmed that he's in the building.
所有人准备好
All teams hold your position.
已经确认目标
We got confirmation.
搞定了吗?
Is it done?
是
Yes.
好的 先别挂
All right. Stay on the line.
阿尔梅达.
Almeida
仔细听我说 阿尔梅达探员
Listen to me very carefully, Agent Almeida.
你是谁?
Who's this?
我是斯蒂芬 桑德斯
It's Stephen Saunders.
在你做错误决定前 我得告诉你一些新情况
Before you make any tactical errors, I'd like to give you an update on the situation.
你说
I'm listening.
我要你到一个没人的地方 和现场作战队直接联系
I need you to move to a private area that has direct comm. with your teams on site here.
我为什么要这样做?
And why would I do that?
打开一个网络端口 连接IP地址 257.211.16.5 你就会知道
Open a web socket to IP 257.211.16.5, and you will find out.
IP地址 257.211.16.5
That's IP 257.211.16.5.
相信我
Just trust me.
照做就是了
Do it.
顺便提一下 托尼 我得恭喜你夫人逃过了病毒这么一劫
By the way, Tony. I'd like to offer you congratulations on your wife eluding infection from the virus.
你怎么知道我妻子的事的?
How do you know about my wife?
访问那个地址
Get on that site.
我不清楚他们在对她作什么 托尼
I don't know exactly what they are doing to her, Tony.
但我提醒过他们 别伤害她 我们好把她还给你
But I did instruct them to leave her barely functional so that we can return her to you.
我要杀了你 你这个狗娘养的
I'll kill you, son of a bitch.
我要割断你的喉咙
I will rip your dam throat out.
听见没有?
You hear me?
我现在时运低 说错什么 你可别怪我
I am low on time, so I am sorry if I brush past that remark.
因为在15秒之后 如果你不照我说的做 我就立马杀了米歇尔
Because in 15 seconds, Michelle will be dead if you don't do what I say.
这栋楼东北角有5名探员在把守
There are 5 agents watching the northeast exit of this building.
地面上4个 一个狙击手在隔壁的楼顶
4 on the ground, a sniper on the rooftop next door.
我猜他们是一个作战组
I am assuming they are operating as a single unit.
我要你发布9号命令 让他们冲进前门
I want you to give them a code 9, send them to the front entrance.
现在
Now.
杰克·鲍尔是这次行动的指挥
Jack Bauer's running the operation.
我没权力这么做
I don't have the authority to do that.
没权力?
No authority?
真的?
Really?
凯文 米歇尔还清醒吗?
Kevin, is Michelle still conscious?
对
Yes
挖掉一只眼睛
Take an eye out.
不 等等 别
No, wait, stop.
凯文 稍等一下
Kevin, hold for a second.
你得给我点时间
It's gonna take me some time.
给你30秒
You have 30 seconds.
格里 这种恐怖的东西正在各地蔓延
Gerry, we are talking about mass hysteria spreading out all over the place.
现在 我们根本寸步难行
Now, we are not in any position to mobilize...
这无关紧要
It doesn't matter.
我们得让公众明白怎么回事
Our position is to let the public know what is going on.
我是贝克
This is Baker.
我是托尼·阿尔梅达
This is Tony Almeida.
切换到3频道
Switch to channel 3.
好了
Go ahead.
执行9号命令
We need you to code 9 your team.
我要你使用一个安全的频道 防止桑德斯偷听
I want you to use a controlled channel in case Saunders is listening.
现在怎么做?
What are we doing?
所有人立刻向前门移动
Move everyone to the front now.
我一直在注意所有频道
I have been monitoring all channels.
前门没有任何情况
There's nothing going on in front.
我们刚刚得到最新卫星资料 杰克还不知道
We just got a new SAT feed that Jack doesn't have yet.
桑德斯好像正向我们的战术盲区移动
Looks like Saunders is on the move in a blind spot.
马上过去
Get there now.
收到 反恐局所有人跟我来
Roger that. 4 CTU personnel diverting to new mark.
不 贝克 不是
No, Baker. Negative.
不光是反恐局的人 所有人
No, not just CTU personnel, everyone.
警局的人也包括 现在过去
Police control included. Get there now.
第4组 执行9号命令 重复一遍 9号命令
Unit 4, we have a code 9.Repeat, code 9.
所有人立刻到前门去
Everyone to the front of the building now.
上车 到前门去
Get in your car, move to the front of the building.
下来 下来
Down, down